Uh, what did what did we do?
You know, my face was cut because somebody was watching the map.
There are two fundamental things that are happening.
Taiwan is the home of our treasured partners.
This is in fact where everything NVIDIA does begins.
Our partners and ourselves take it to the world.
Taiwan and our partnership has created the world's AI infrastructure.
These are really, really exciting times.
A restart of our computer industry.
A industry that you have forged.
A industry that you have created.
And now you're prepared for the next major journey.
I love you guys.
It's a new industrial revolution.
And you'll also have a beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful
So this video I will be able to translate
and
to
why I am going to do this series of
speaking of this series of
I believe that I will be able to use AI
and industry
will be the time of the time
and I hope you can hear these
these
after you will be more
more
less
I hope you will like it.
Examples of the use cases and then seeing it in action.
That's kind of the flow.
It's such a compelling story.
I'm super nervous about this.
Just gotta get in the rhythm.
We're two weeks away from it.
You guys can go really, really make a break.
We should take a swing at it.
Yeah, that's the plan.
I think we need to have daily status on that animation.
Can you mute? Because I hear myself.
Sorry.
What's the drop date for all the videos?
It needs to be done on the 28th.
Did you get all that?
Safe travels, everybody.
Super excited to see everyone.
See you guys soon.
Okay. Bye.
We're basically moving as fast as the world can absorb technology.
So we've got to leave for them ourselves.
This isn't right.
Now the spine, you just have to figure out a way to make it pop.
You know what I'm saying?
You want to go?
Yeah.
That kind of thing.
You know what I'm saying?
You want to go?
Yeah.
That kind of thing.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm super late.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I'm super late.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I'm super late.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I'm super late.
Let's go.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm super late.
Let's go.
Please welcome to the stage NVIDIA founder and CEO, Jensen Wang.
I am very happy to be back.
Thank you NTU for letting us use your stadium.
The last time I was here, I received a degree from NTU.
And I gave the run, don't walk speech.
And today we have a lot to cover.
So I cannot walk, I must run.
I'm very happy to be here in Taiwan.
Taiwan is the home of our treasured partners.
This is in fact where everything NVIDIA does begins.
Our partners and ourselves take it to the world.
Taiwan and our partnership has created the world's AI infrastructure.
These are really, really exciting times.
A restart of our computer industry.
An industry that you have forged.
An industry that you have created.
And now you're prepared for the next major journey.
I want to speak to you in Chinese.
But I have so much to tell you.
I have to think too hard to speak Chinese.
So I have to speak to you in English.
Two fundamental technologies.
Accelerated computing and artificial intelligence running inside the omniverse.
Those two technologies, those two fundamental forces of computing are going to reshape the computer industry.
The computer industry is now some 60 years old.
In a lot of ways, everything that we do today was invented the year after my birth in 1964.
All of the things that we know today about computing largely described in 1964.
Of course, the PC revolution democratized computing and put it in the hands and the houses of everybody.
And then in 2007, the iPhone introduced mobile computing and put the computer in our pocket.
Ever since, everything is connected and running all the time through the mobile cloud.
This last 60 years, we saw several, just several, not that many actually, two or three major technology shifts.
Two or three tectonic shifts in computing where everything changed.
And we're about to see that happen again.
There are two fundamental things that are happening.
The first is that the processor, the engine by which the computer industry runs on, the central processing unit, the performance scaling has slowed tremendously.
And yet, the amount of computation we have to do is still doubling very quickly, exponentially.
If processing requirement, if the data that we need to process continues to scale exponentially, but performance does not, we will experience computation inflation.
And in fact, we're seeing that right now as we speak.
The amount of data center power that's used all over the world is growing quite substantially.
The cost of computing is growing.
We are seeing computation inflation.
This, of course, cannot continue.
The data is going to continue to increase exponentially and CPU performance scaling will never return.
There is a better way.
For almost two decades now, we've been working on accelerated computing.
Just last week, Google announced that they put QDF in the cloud and accelerate Pandas.
Pandas is the most popular data science library in the world.
Many of you in here probably already use Pandas.
It's used by 10 million data scientists in the world.
Downloaded 170 million times each month.
It is the Excel that is the spreadsheet of data scientists.
Well, with just one click, the speed up is really incredible.
Let's take a look.
That was a great demo, right?
It didn't take long.
It's Earth 2.
The idea that we would create a digital twin of the Earth, that we would go and simulate
the Earth so that we could predict the future of our planet to better avert disasters or better
understand the impact of climate change so that we can adapt better, so that we could change
our habits now.
On Monday, the storm will veer north again and approach Taiwan.
There are big uncertainties regarding its path.
Different paths will have different levels of impact on Taiwan.
And also, the other Penn State Trust.
And also, the Penn State Trust.
The core div is a nvidia-like design model.
It is a design model for the WRF-based model.
It can be used to build a higher-level
!
And you can also grow into the beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful
And also into the impact of the beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful
And the otherinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinchinch
The truth is that was a Jensen AI.
That was not me.
We dedicated ourselves to reinvent everything.
That was 10 years ago now.
And all of it came together on a brand new computer nobody understood.
Nobody asked for it. Nobody understood it.
And in fact, I was certain nobody wanted to buy it.
And so we announced it at GTC and OpenAI, a small company in San Francisco saw it.
And they asked me to deliver one to them.
I delivered the first DGX, the world's first AI supercomputer to OpenAI in 2016.
And then in November 2022, trained on thousands, tens of thousands of NVIDIA GPUs in a very large AI supercomputer, OpenAI announced ChatGPT.
One million users after five days. One million after five days. A hundred million after two months.
The fastest growing application in history. And the reason for that is very simple.
It is just so easy to use. And it was so magical to use.
To be able to interact with a computer like it's human.
Instead of being clear about what you want. It's like the computer understands your meaning.
It understands your intention.
Oh, I think here it asks the closest night market.
Night, as you know, the night market is very important to me.
So when I was young, I was, I think I was four and a half years old.
I used to love going to the night market because I just love watching people.
And, and, and, and so we went, my parents used to take us to the night market.
And I love, I love, I love going. And one day, my face, you guys might, might see that I have a large scar on my face.
My face was cut because somebody was washing their knife and I was a little kid.
But my memories of, of the night market is so deep because of that.
And I used to love, I just, I still love going to the night market.
And I just need to tell you guys this.
The, the Tonghua, a night market is, is really good because there's a lady.
She's been working there for 43 years.
She's the fruit lady.
And it's in the middle of the street, the middle between the two.
Go find her.
Okay.
She, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she.
She's really terrific.
I think it would be funny after this, all of you go to see her.
She, every year she's doing better and better.
Her car tests improved and, yeah, I just love watching her succeed.
Anyways, anyways, ChatGPT came along until ChatGPT revealed it to the world.
AI was all about perception, natural language understanding, computer vision, speech recognition.
It's all about perception and detection.
This was the first time the world saw a generative AI.
It produced tokens, one token at a time.
And those tokens were words.
Some of the tokens, of course, could now be images or charts or tables, songs, words, speech, videos.
Those tokens could be anything.
Anything that, that you can learn the meaning of.
It could be tokens of chemicals, tokens of proteins, genes.
You saw earlier in Earth 2, we were generating tokens of the weather.
We can use this method to generate tokens for almost anything.
Almost anything of value.
We can generate steering wheel control for a car.
We can generate articulation for a robotic arm.
Everything that we can learn, we can now generate.
We have now arrived, not at the AI era, but a generative AI era.
But what's really important is this.
This computer that started out as a super computer has now evolved into a data center.
And it produces one thing.
It produces tokens.
It's an AI factory.
This AI factory is generating, creating, producing something of great value.
A new commodity.
In the late 1890s, Nikola Tesla invented an AC generator.
We invented an AI generator.
The AC generator generated electrons.
NVIDIA's AI generator generates tokens.
Both of these things have large market opportunities.
It's completely fungible in almost every industry.
And that's why it's a new industrial revolution.
We have now a new factory producing a new commodity for every industry that is of extraordinary value.
And the methodology for doing this is quite scalable.
And the methodology of doing this is quite repeatable.
Notice how quickly so many different AI models, generative AI models, are being invented.
Literally daily.
Every single industry is now piling on.
And the industry is now piling on.
For the very first time, the IT industry, which is $3 trillion.
$3 trillion IT industry is about to create something that can directly serve $100 trillion of industry.
No longer just an instrument for information storage or data processing, but a factory for generating intelligence for every industry.
This is going to be a manufacturing industry.
Not a manufacturing industry of computers, but using the computers in manufacturing.
This has never happened before.
Quite an extraordinary thing.
What started with accelerated computing led to AI, led to generative AI, and now an industrial revolution.
One of the most important applications in the coming future, of course, is customer service agents.
Customer service agents are necessary in just about every single industry.
It represents trillions of dollars of customer service around the world.
Nurses are customer service agents in some ways.
Some of them are non-prescription or non-diagnostic based nurses.
Are essentially customer service.
Customer service for retail, for quick service foods, financial services, insurance.
Just tens and tens of millions of customer service can now be augmented by language models and augmented by AI.
And so these boxes that you see are basically NIMS.
Some of the NIMS are reasoning agents.
Given a task, figure out what the mission is, break it down into a plan.
Some of the NIMS retrieve information.
Some of the NIMS might go and do search.
So all of these NIMS are experts that are now assembled as a team.
So what's happening?
The application layer has been changed.
What used to be applications written with instructions are now applications that are assembling teams.
Assembling teams of AIs.
Very few people know how to write programs.
Almost everybody knows how to break down a problem and assemble teams.
Every company, I believe in the future, will have a large collection of NIMS.
And you would bring down the experts that you want.
You connect them into a team.
And you don't even have to figure out exactly how to connect them.
You just give the mission to an agent, to a NIMS to figure out who to break the task down and who to give it to.
And that central, the leader of the application, if you will, the leader of the team, would break down the task and give it to the various team members.
The team members would perform their task, bring it back to the team leader.
The team leader would reason about that and present an information back to you.
Just like humans.
Great to be in Taiwan.
Before I head out to the night market, let's dive into some exciting frontiers of digital humans.
Imagine a future where computers interact with us just like humans can.
Hi, my name is Sophie and I am a digital human brand ambassador for Unique.
This is the incredible reality of digital humans.
Digital humans will revolutionize industries from customer service to advertising and gaming.
The possibilities for digital humans are endless.
Using the scans you took of your current kitchen with your phone.
They will be AI interior designers, helping generate beautiful, photorealistic suggestions and sourcing the materials and furniture.
We have generated several design options for you to choose from.
They will also be AI customer service agents, making the interaction more engaging and personalized.
Or digital healthcare workers who will check on patients, providing timely, personalized care.
I did forget to mention to the doctor that I am allergic to penicillin.
Is it still okay to take the medications?
The antibiotics you've been prescribed, ciprofloxacin and metronidazole, don't contain penicillin.
So it's perfectly safe for you to take them.
And they'll even be AI brand ambassadors, setting the next marketing and advertising trends.
Hi, I'm Ima, Japan's first virtual model.
New breakthroughs in generative AI and computer graphics let digital humans see, understand and interact with us in human-like ways.
Hmm, from what I can see, it looks like you're in some kind of recording or production setup.
The foundation of digital humans are AI models built on multilingual speech recognition and synthesis.
And LLMs that understand and generate conversation.
We have a full-time practice of spiritual dance and traditional dance.
We have a full-time practice of spiritual dance and the most natural.
The AI's connect to another generative AI to dynamically animate a life-like 3D mesh of a face.
And finally, AI models that reproduce lifelike appearances.
Enabling real-time path-traced subsurface scattering to simulate the way light penetrates the skin, scatters and exits at various points.
Giving skin its soft and translucent appearance.
NVIDIA ACE is a suite of digital human technologies packaged as easy to deploy fully optimized microservices or NIMS.
Developers can integrate ACE NIMS into their existing frameworks, engines and digital human experiences.
NEMOTRON SLM and LLM NIMS to understand our intent and orchestrate other models.
RIVA Speech NIMS for interactive speech and translation.
Audio to face and gesture NIMS for facial and body animation.
And Omniverse RTX with DLSS for neural rendering of skin and hair.
ACE NIMS run on NVIDIA GDN.
A global network of NVIDIA accelerated infrastructure that delivers low latency digital human processing to over 100 regions.
Every single time data generation grows, the amount of computation that we have to offer needs to grow with it.
We are about to enter a phase where AIs can learn the laws of physics and understand and be grounded in physical world data.
And so we expect that models will continue to grow.
And we need larger GPUs.
Well, Blackwell was designed for this generation.
This is Blackwell.
And has several very important technologies.
One, of course, is just the size of the chip.
We took two of the largest, a chip that is as large as you can make it at TSMC, and we connected two of them together.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is Blackwell.
Blackwell is in production.
Incredible amounts of technology.
This is the MGX system, and here's the two Blackwell boards.
So this one node has four Blackwell chips.
Let me talk about what's next.
The next wave of AI is physical AI.
AI that understands the laws of physics.
AI that can work among us.
And so they have to understand the world model so that they understand how to interpret the world, how to perceive the world.
They have to, of course, have excellent cognitive capabilities so they can understand us, understand what we asked, and perform the tasks.
In the future, robotics is a much more pervasive idea.
Of course, when I say robotics, there's a humanoid robotics that's usually the representation of that.
But that's not at all true.
Everything is going to be robotic.
All of the factories will be robotic.
The factories will orchestrate robots.
And those robots will be building products that are robotic.
Robots interacting with robots, building products that are robotic.
The era of robotics has arrived.
One day, everything that moves will be autonomous.
Researchers and companies around the world are developing robots powered by physical AI.
Physical AIs are models that can understand instructions and autonomously perform complex tasks in the real world.
Multimodal LLMs are breakthroughs that enable robots to learn, perceive, and understand the world around them, and plan how they'll act.
And from human demonstrations, robots can now learn the skills required to interact with the world using gross and fine motor skills.
One of the integral technologies for advancing robotics is reinforcement learning.
Just as LLMs need RLHF, or reinforcement learning from human feedback, to learn particular skills,
Generative physical AI can learn skills using reinforcement learning from physics feedback in a simulated world.
These simulation environments are where robots learn to make decisions by performing actions in a virtual world that obeys the laws of physics.
In these robot gyms, a robot can learn to perform complex and dynamic tasks safely and quickly,
Refining their skills through millions of acts of trial and error.
We built NVIDIA Omniverse as the operating system where physical AIs can be created.
Omniverse is a development platform for virtual world simulation, combining real-time, physically-based rendering,
Physics simulation, and generative AI technologies.
In Omniverse, robots can learn how to be robots.
They learn how to autonomously manipulate objects with precision, such as grasping and handling objects.
Or navigate environments autonomously, finding optimal paths while avoiding obstacles and hazards.
Learning in Omniverse minimizes the sim-to-real gap and maximizes the transfer of learned behavior.
Building robots with generative physical AI requires three computers.
NVIDIA AI supercomputers to train the models.
NVIDIA Jetson Oren and next-generation Jetson Thor robotic supercomputer to run the models.
And NVIDIA Omniverse where robots can learn and refine their skills in simulated worlds.
We build the platforms, acceleration libraries, and AI models needed by developers and companies.
And allow them to use any or all of the stacks that suit them best.
The next wave of AI is here.
Robotics powered by physical AI will revolutionize industries.
This is happening all over Taiwan.
Foxconn is building digital twins of their factories.
Delta is building digital twins of their factories.
By the way, half is real, half is digital, half is Omniverse.
Pegatron is building digital twins of their robotic factories.
Wishtron is building digital twins of their robotic factories.
And this is really cool.
This is a video of Foxconn's new factory.
Let's take a look.
Foxconn, the world's largest electronics manufacturer, is gearing up to meet this demand
by building robotic factories with NVIDIA Omniverse and AI.
Factory planners use Omniverse to integrate facility and equipment data from leading industry applications
like Siemens Teamcenter X and Autodesk Revit.
In the digital twin, they optimize floor layout and line configurations
and locate optimal camera placements to monitor future operations
with NVIDIA Metropolis powered Vision AI.
Virtual integration saves planners on the enormous cost of physical change orders.
During construction, the Foxconn teams use the digital twin as the source of truth
to communicate and validate accurate equipment layout.
The Omniverse digital twin is also the robot gym,
where Foxconn developers train and test NVIDIA ISAAC AI applications
for robotic perception and manipulation,
and Metropolis AI applications for sensor fusion.
In Omniverse, Foxconn simulates two robot AI's before deploying runtimes to Jetson computers.
On the assembly line, they simulate ISAAC manipulator libraries and AI models
for automated optical inspection for object identification, defect detection, and trajectory planning.
To transfer HGX systems to the test pods, they simulate ISAAC perceptor powered Ferobot AMRs
as they perceive and move about their environment with 3D mapping and reconstruction.
With Omniverse, Foxconn builds their robotic factories that orchestrate robots running on NVIDIA ISAAC
to build NVIDIA AI supercomputers, which in turn train Foxconn's robots.
Taiwan builds computers with keyboards.
You build computers for your pocket.
You build computers for data centers in the cloud.
In the future, you're going to build computers that walk and computers that roll, you know, around.
And so these are all just computers.
And as it turns out, the technology is very similar to the technology of building all of the other computers
that you already built today.
So this is going to be a really extraordinary journey for us.
Well, I want to thank...
I want to...
I want to thank...
I've made one last video, if you don't mind.
Taiwan,
幫助我們實現了一個願景.
在這條漫長的路上,
無數的夥伴支持著我們,
從加速運算、電腦繪圖、科學研究到人工智慧的高峰,
每一個晶片、每一台電腦都描寫著你們辛勤工作和追求完美的故事。
台灣是無名的英雄,
確實世界的支柱。
一起,我們推動了產業的復興。
辛勤的耕耘讓我們能夠踏入佔新運算的領域。
其中,我們製作的電腦會轉化成新型的工廠,
製造珍貴無比的人工智慧。
親愛的夥伴們,
你們是AI產業革新的後盾。
無論面對多大的風浪,
你始終穩如磐石。
科技的卓越、
勤奮與其心合力的精神,
是你的超能力。
沒有你,
我們的願景只是一個無法實現的夢想。
與你同行,
我們勇往直前。
創造智慧與便利的生活,
對抗疾病和自然災害,
讓我們的世界變得更美好。
謝謝你,台灣。
讓我們繼續為這段AI創新之旅,
打造一個成功和繁榮的產業。
大家謝謝,
謝謝。
我愛你們,謝謝。
大家謝謝。
謝謝。
我愛你們,謝謝。